Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Faculty Reference Collection1845-present
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
University at Albany Foundation
ua950.003
42.25 cubic ft.
Reference file of former and current UAlbany faculty members.
Biographical History
The University at Albany has a long history dating back to 1844 when it was established as the New York State Normal School to train teachers. The faculty have always played a major role in the school though its time as a small state liberal arts college and its evolution into a major public research institution.
Scope and Contents
This collection was originally a file created and used by the UAlbany Foundation, a nonprofit fundraising corporation for the University at Albany, SUNY. The "faculty file" was transferred to the University Archives where is serves as a general reference source for former and current faculty members.
File contain news articles, clippings, faculty curriculum vitae (CV), and other promotional or public relations material. This collection does not contain any personnel records or private information.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection has no series, organized alphabetically by last name.
Acquisition Information
The vast majority items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by the University at Albany Foundation.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guide for Criminal Justice and Prisons.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Faculty (Education); public relations; Clippings (information artifacts); promotional documents; University at Albany Foundation.; State University of New York at Albany.
- Aarnio, Johan, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Abdo, Baaklini - Director of the Center for Legislative Development, Public Affairs and Policy (1972-1990) (1990-2003) (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Abelson, Laurie, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Able, Kenneth - Biology Department, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Abrams, Jay H. (1971-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Abraham, J. Philippe, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Abramson, Julie, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Aceto, Vincent John, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Acker, James R., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Acosta- Belen, Edna, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Adams, Harold W. - Department of Public Affairs (1966-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Adams, Harriet, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Adams, Theodore S. (1959-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Addotta, Antionette E. - Librarian, University Libraries (1980-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Affinito, Stephanie, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Agee, Jane Murray, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Agrawal, Rajendra K., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Aguilar, Edwin, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Aguirre- Ghiso, Julio, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Ahmad, Shamshad, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Aken, Rita - Hispanic and Italian Studies (1981-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Akullian, Agnes - College Nursing Services, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Alam, Mohammad S. - Department of Physics (1984-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Alba, Richard, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Albagli, Richard - Music Department Composer-Percusionist (1974-) (1942-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Albano, Dr. Anne Marie - Center for Stress and Anxiety Disorders, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Aldrich, Margaret H. - Assistant Director Student Activities (1981-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Alexander II, Douglas - French, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Alexander, Franklin - Art Department, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Alexander, John W. - Placement Offices (1977-1984), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Aliotti, Nicholas C. - School of Education (1970-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Allaud, Guy D. - Department of Mathematics (1968,1969-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Allard, Wilfred P., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Allen, Gary, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Allen, Donald, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Allen, Laurel, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Allen, Richard L. - Department of Rhetoric and Communications (1978-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Allen, Wayne - Physical Plant, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Alliger, George, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Allington, Richard, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Alonso, Damaso - Spanish Department, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Alonso-Regalado, Jesus - History Subject Librarian, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Alrutz, Daniel J. - Plant Department (1977-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Altrock, Barbara, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Altarriba, Jeanette, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Alvar, Manuel - Hispanic and Italian Studies (1988-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Alvord, Gregory, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Ambach, Gordon M., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Anastasiow, Mary A., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Anderson, Carl, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Anderson, Carol L., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Andersen, David F., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Andersen, Deborah Lines, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Andersen, Robert Niels, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Anderson, Drew A., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Anderson Francis H., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Anderson, James A., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Anderson, Janet, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Anderson, Thomas C., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Andrasik, Frank, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Andrea, Robert K., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Andrews, Linda O., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Andreyewsky, Alexander, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Angus, Johnnie Gillespie, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Angelis, Janet, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Angell, George, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Anolik, Boris, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Applebum, Hannah B., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Applebee, Arthur, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Applegate, Mary, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Arana- Downs, Ruben, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Arbitman, Idal, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Archambeault, Deborah, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Archer, Jeffrey - Business Bibliographer, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Arden, Dean N., Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 75)
- Arensberg, Mary, Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 76)
- Armlin, Nelson J. - CASDA (1977-), Undated (Box 1 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 77)
- Armour-Garb, Brad, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Armstrong, Donna, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Armstrong, Roberta, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Armstrong, Ronald E., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Arnason, Geirmunder, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Arnason, John, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Arnold, Donald F., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Aronson, John Noel, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Arterburn, Alfred B., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Asermely, Albert, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Ashberry, John N., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Astiz, Carlos, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Atiya, Snmer, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Atkinson, Steven D., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Auclair, Jean-Louis, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Auclair, Lois Gregg, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- August, Debra J., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Auricchio, Pasquale (Pat), Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Austin, Bill, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Austin, Sandra, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Avant, Deborah, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Averyt, Bennet, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Avisar, Ilan, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Axelrod, Donald, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Baaklini, Abdo, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Bacher, Frank Jr., 1997 (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Baer, Judith A., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Baglioni, Corrado, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Bailey, Bruce, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Bailey, Elaine M., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Bailey, Frankie, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Bakhru, Hassaram, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Balaban, Miriam, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Baldwin, Alexinia, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Baldwin, Alexinia, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Balk, Walter L., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Balk, Walter L., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Ballard, Allen, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Ballou, Donald P., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Ban, Carolyn, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Bank, Shelton, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Baran, Henryk, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Barker, Thomas, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Barker-Benfield, Graham J., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Barker-Flynn, Holly, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Barlau, Stephen B., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Barlow, David H., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Barnard, Stephen, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Barnard, Sylvia, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Barnes-Ostrander, Marilyn, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Barnett, Thomas R., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Barone, Sandro A., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Barreto, Ernesto, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Barry, David G., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Barry, J.K.M., 1917 (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Barth, Michael E., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Bartow, Jonathan, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Bashkoff, Jacueline, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Bass, Thomas, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Bates, Pamela A., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Baum, Maude, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Baum, Rachel, Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Baum, Werner C., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Bayer, Theodore J., Undated (Box 2 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Baxley, DiAnn, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Beauchamp, Dan, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Bechet, Paul, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Beck, Thomas D., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Becker, Wendy, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Bedian, Judy, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Beditz, Steve, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Beeten, Scott, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Begam, Ann G., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Begg, Nancy, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Begley, Thomas, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Beharriell, Frederick J., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Beckhard, Mozaffar, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Belanger, Michele, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Belardo, Salvatore, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Belasen, Alan, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Belding, S.B., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Belfort, Marlene, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Bell, Robert, 1954-1966 (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Belowich-Negron, Nancy, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Benade, Arthur, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Benedict, Marjorie, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Benedict, Peter C., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Benenson, Raymond E., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Benezet, Louis T., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Benitez, Margarita, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- But, Benjamin, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Bennett, Peter, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Benson, Gregory, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Benson-Wright, Penelope, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Berenguer, A., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Berg, Lawrence K., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Bergau, Nancy, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Berger, Mark, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Berger, Morris I., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Berger, Morris I., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Berger, Ron, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Berger, Sheila, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Berger, Sheila, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Bergeson, Clarance O., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Bergin, Thomas, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Berkowitz, Joel, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Berkun, Howard, 1969 April 24 (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Berman, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Bernier, Joseph Jr., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Bernstein, Roberta, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Berry, Leonard J., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Bers, Melvin K., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Bessette, Tom, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Bethea, Mahaliel "J.R.", Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Bettelheim, Bruno, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Betz, Margaret, 1959 (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Biggs, Donald A., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Bingham, Sarah M., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Birchenough, Harry, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Birckbichler, Diane, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Birge, Scott R., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Birkhead, Guthrie, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)
- Birkland, Thomas, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 57)
- Birn, Donald, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 58)
- Birr, Kendall A., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 59)
- Bjarnason, Thor, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 60)
- Black, Michael, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 61)
- Blair, Mary Grace, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 62)
- Blais, Archie, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 63)
- Blaisdell, Kenneth, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 64)
- Blanchard, Duncan, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 65)
- Blanchard, Edward, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 66)
- Blanton, Hart, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 67)
- Blatner, Barbara A., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 68)
- Blau, Judith, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 69)
- Blau, Peter, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 70)
- Bleiberg, German, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 71)
- Bleichert, Henry, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 72)
- Blotcher, Donald H., Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 73)
- Block Eric, Undated (Box 3 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 74)
- Blodgett, Hollis F., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 1)
- Blodgett, Royann S., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 2)
- Blood, Susan, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 3)
- Bloniarz, Peter, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 4)
- Blount, Stanley, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 5)
- Blue, Leonard A., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 6)
- Blum, Mark L., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 7)
- Blum, Terry, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 8)
- Blumenthal, Joel, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 9)
- Boahm, Anne E., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 10)
- Bockhorst, Diane, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 11)
- Boehm, Thomas Allen, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 12)
- Boice, Robert, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 13)
- Bolce, Robert, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 14)
- Boll, Jennifer, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 15)
- Bonk, Sharon, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 16)
- Boomsliter, Paul C., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 17)
- Boomsliter, Paul C., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 18)
- Boomsliter, Paul C., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 19)
- Bonawitz, Irving M., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 20)
- Bond, Dorcas, 1970 March 7 (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 21)
- Bonnor, Florence, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 22)
- Bonventre, Vincent, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 23)
- Boots, Michael, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 24)
- Bord, Nancy, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 25)
- Borys, Ted, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 26)
- Bosart, Lance F., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 27)
- Bosco, Joseph, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 28)
- Bouchard, Bruce, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 29)
- Bouchard, Christine, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 30)
- Bowles, Brett, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 31)
- Bowen, John H., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 32)
- Bowman, Charles L., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 33)
- Bowman, Joseph Jr., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 34)
- Boyd, Kathryn, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 35)
- Boyer, Ernest L., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 36)
- Boyer, Ernest L., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 37)
- Bradbury, John L., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 38)
- Bradish, Gaynor F., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 39)
- Bradt, Douglass, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 40)
- Brady, George, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 41)
- Braithwaite, Bernard S., 1963 Summer (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 42)
- Brannon, Lillian, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 43)
- Bravos, Theodore, 1973 (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 44)
- Bray, William G., Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 45)
- Bredderman, Theodore, 1986 (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 46)
- Breen, Joan, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 47)
- Breitbart, Yuri, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 48)
- Brewer, George E., 1964 (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 49)
- Brewer, Floyd Irving, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 50)
- Briand, Kevin, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 51)
- Briar-Lawson, Katharine, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 52)
- Brickman, Leonard, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 53)
- Brickman, Louis, 1967 (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 54)
- Brickman, Louis, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 55)
- Briere, Jean-Francois, Undated (Box 4 (Faculty Reference Collection), Folder 56)